yeah yeah
got a stack of blanket sets by my stereo deck
gonna stay up late what the heck the dj's voice is
a trusted friend on the signal that will never
end he's playing all the hits i know putting on a
late night show just for me and And all the other
kids living life out on the skids We're living on
the radio waves tonight Everything's gonna be
alright Just turn it up, don't let it fade A
perfect memory being made Yeah, we're living on
the radio waves
Got my finger on the record and the pause
Breaking all of gravity's laws Gotta get the
timing just right to make a perfect mix Taping
the fading light for a long drive In a beat-up car
underneath a million stars This plastic box of
tangled thread Holds every single word we say
We're living on the radio waves tonight
Everything's gonna be alright Just turn it up,
don't let it fade A perfect memory being made
Yeah, we're living on the radio waves
We're living on the radio waves tonight
Everything's gonna be alright Just turn it up,
don't let it fade A perfect memory being made
Yeah, we're living on the radio waves